rebelbetting.com 2016-12-14

# Privacy Policy | Sports Arbitrage – RebelBetting

#### General principles

RebelBetting and ClaroBet AB is committed to having the highest possible standards of online privacy and security. This privacy statement explains how we will do this.

#### Collected information

When registering your username and password, you will only need to submit your email. Your IP address will in some cases be logged. No other information is collected by ClaroBet AB.

If you choose to purchase the full version of RebelBetting you will be forwarded to a selection of payment gateways where you need to be registered with name and address. All payment information (credit card information etc) is handled and stored securely by these payment gateways and can not be accessed by ClaroBet.

The payment pages are securely protected and encrypted by HTTPS/SSL.

#### Sharing of information

ClaroBet AB do not and will never sell or trade your personal information to others.

We keep to our obligations under the Swedish Personal Data Law (Law 1998:204) that relate to holding personal data.

#### Email security

ClaroBet AB will never send unsolicited email. All newsletter signups requires a double opt-in. 

#### RebelBetting security

The RebelBetting software communicates with our servers to provide the user with sports arbitrage opportunities. The only information being sent to our servers is the RebelBetting username and password for authentication (both encrypted). Bookmaker usernames or passwords are never sent.

Sensitive information stored in RebelBetting like bookmaker login information is stored on the user’s computer using a master password and a “salt” with an industrial strength encryption.

Optionally, starting the program can require the master password to be entered. This means that even if your computer is compromised, the sensitive information is safe.  
(The master password can also be remembered and will then be saved encrypted bound to your machine and Windows account, we do not recommend this if you want maximum security).

Both our software and our web site is signed by certificates verifying ClaroBet AB as the owner. The software certificate also verifies that the software has not been tampered with since release.

The website rebelbetting.com and our downloads are verified by antivirus service [McAfee SiteAdvisor](http://www.siteadvisor.com/sites/rebelbetting.com).

#### Web site security

Any personal information is encoded using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology before being sent over the Internet.

#### Use of Cookies

Cookies are small files which many web sites transfer to your hard disk. They can inform the web site what pages you visit, and your preferences, which enable web sites to provide you with a more personalized service. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you before accepting them. Cookies are currently not required at rebelbetting.com.

This privacy statement is subject to change without prior notice.
